(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T02:12:43.540409",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
曖昧3センチ
Around three centimeters,
そりゃぷにってコトかい？
and that's squishy? Yeah right!
ちょっ！
Wait!
らっぴんぐが制服
My wrapping is a uniform...
だぁぁ不利ってこたぁない
...there's no disadvantage to it,
ぷ。
pfft.
がんばっちゃ
I'll give it my best,
やっちゃっちゃ
I'll do it!
そんときゃーっち
In times like that, it's catch...
＆ Release
...and release!
ぎょっ
Whoa!
汗 フッフッ の谷間に
In the gap between drops of sweat,
Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
もってけ！セーラーふく
Take It! Sailor Uniform
なんかだるー
I feel kinda sluggish,
なんかでるー
I feel kinda out of it,
あいしてるー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
...wait, one of those is different!
悩みん坊ー
Worry-wart,
高鉄棒ー
high bar,
おいしん簿ー
gourmet...
いーかげんにシナサイ
...cut it out!
飛んでったアイツの
About the flushed body...
火照るカラダって
...of that girl who jumped,
いわゆる普通の女の子
she's just a so-called "normal" girl.
驚いたあたしだけ？
Am I the only one who was surprised?
豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだ
Another helping of extra-firm tonkotsu noodles!
BON-BON おーえん団
Bon-bon, we're cheerleaders!
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN かんげー会
Ran-ran, a welcome party!
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation!
はい！存在感 テンションMAX ぶつかって溶けました呆然
Yes! Presence, tension MAX! We bumped and melted, dumbfounded!
おい！追いかけっこだって知れんじゃん！
Hey! You know it's a game of chase!
持っていけ！最後に笑っちゃうのはアタシのはず
Take it away! The one laughing in the end is bound to be me!
セーラー服だからです 結論！
Because it's a sailor uniform, that's the conclusion!
月曜日なのに機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
What should we do about being in a bad mood even though it's Monday?
夏服が良いのです 可愛い！
Summer uniforms are the best, so cute!
制服？賛成！それ真似っこしちゃだーめ！よん
Uniform? Approved! Don't go copying that! Four!
がんばって！はりきって！マイダーリンダーリン please!
Do your best! Get excited! My darling, darling, please!
もりあがり もりさがり 恋したり まだ内緒にしといて倫理
High spirits, low spirits, falling in love, keep it a secret for now, ethics!
甘えん坊 用心棒 通信簿 頂戴して玉砕！
Spoiled kid, bodyguard, report card, receiving it and shattering!
ぷにっとアースに吸い込まれたいって 大げさちんたらくりくり
Saying you want to be sucked into the squishy Earth, overexaggerating, dilly-dallying, round and round!
ぜったい残留一等賞 なまいき すりおろし おねだりだだだだ
Definitely staying behind first prize! Cheeky, grated, begging da-da-da-da!
おんおんそーれー れっつごーあらし
On-on-sole, let's go storm!
やんやんそーだん ぷっつんかっつんてんてーしょん おい！
Yan-yan-discussion, snapping and cracking, tension! Hey!
そう失敬 全然アルバイト
Oh, excuse me, a complete part-time job!
探したら見つかって当然 人生まるっとケれなーし
Of course I'll find one if I look, you can't just kick all of life away!
やってみな 新規に狙っちゃうのはアタシの挑戦！
Give it a try! Targeting anew is my challenge!
セーラー服着替えてもアタシ 週末はどうよ？
Even if I change out of my sailor uniform, I'm still me! How about the weekend?
ちら見せなんてありきたり 制服は簡単よ らくちん
Glimpses are so cliché! Uniforms are so easy, effortless!
らくちー！
Effortless!
ほうそくさんせー だきついてえもんだー ぎゅっ
Rule approved! Hugging is good, squeeze!
胸どっき 髪はっぴ マイシュガーシュガースウィート
Heart thumping, hair happy, my sugar sugar sweet!
ぽぽんぽんぺー わしゅっ、う、う、あー
Poponponpe, washutsu, ooh, ooh, ah!
らららん ちょっちょっぴ るっくあっぷ ふっふっはー はい！
La-la-la, slightly, look up, foo-foo-hah! Yes!
えちゅけーしょん のび エブリシン
Education, stretch, everything!
おくだくだ おくだくだ よーよー 晴れて 晴れて へるなーし
Okudakuda, okudakuda, yo-yo, sunny, sunny, herunaashi!
持っていけ！最後に笑っちゃうのはアタシのはず
Take it away! The one laughing in the end is bound to be me!
セーラー服だからです 結論！
Because it's a sailor uniform, that's the conclusion!
月曜日なのに機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
What should we do about being in a bad mood even though it's Monday?
夏服が良いのです 可愛い！
Summer uniforms are the best, so cute!
やっぱり！最後に笑っちゃうのはアタシのはず
Just as I thought! The one laughing in the end is bound to be me!
セーラー服だからです 結論！
Because it's a sailor uniform, that's the conclusion!
あいまい3センチ それぷにってことかい？わお！
An ambiguous three centimeters, does that mean it's squishy? Wow!
らっぴんぐが制服 よしこりってことない？ぽう！
Wrapping is a uniform, isn't that nice? Pow!
がんばっちゃ やっちゃっちゃ あんとっちゃ
Do your best, do it, untouchable!
かぷかぷじゃじゃはー はい！せーのせーの マイダーリンダーリンみゅーず！
Kapu-kapu-ja-ja-hah, yes! Ready, set, my darling darling muse!
Now, this is what I'm talking about!
That's what we need!
We need... we need another hit show!
We need an anime opening!
No! No, we need... No, we need a show! We need... We need something with substance.
I just thought that our show was failing because we didn't have an anime opening.
No, our show is failing because it's really bad.
It's... it's not that bad.
It's really bad! Have you seen the reviews?
They're wrong though. It's an acquired opinion.
Ah... well... oh, that's so complicated. I didn't sign up for this. I'm just... look, I'm eye candy.
See? Woo!
Well, your eye candy isn't getting us any ratings.
Well, yours isn't either! Look at this!
No, stop, stop! No one wants to see that! Stop! We need an idea.
We can both sell ourselves out!
No, that's not going to work, that's not enough. I have an idea.
What?
We steal other people's concepts!
You're a genius!
We just make what's already popular, but...
...make it ours!
Yes!
We'll put our name on it.
Yeah, we'll get all the credit.
What are they going to do? Nothing!
We'll get all the funding back!
And then we can finally do what we're really passionate about!
Oh my god! Oh my god! But we're going to have to... we're going to have to do so much research on what's popular.
What do we do? What do we do? We need... we need influencers.
We need influencers? We need... sexy ladies?
We have that. Oh, wait, we already have that.
We need... what else do we need? Um...
We need to sell out.
Ah... I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres to see the amber green.
Like what?
Every genre.
I think that's the only way.
You're boring me. Kind of...
What?
I was a sympathetic sleeper!
Ah... Huh?
Wait, where are we, Gigi?
What is this?
What is this? Are we... Are we in my head?
Wait, are we in your head? Are we in my head?
This is just like fanfiction!
Does that mean we're going to steal people's ideas?
Oh no, they're our ideas. We're in my head.
I'm going to steal your idea.
You can't steal my ideas.
I could.
Wait, what if... what if I see every single idea that's in your head, and then I take them from you, and then...
If you go too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yaoi parts!
Oh... Oh... Oh, maybe we should start with my brain. It's okay, it's okay. Wait, wait.
What's in your brain?
A thing.
Actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels! We can't put that in our show!
Yes, we can!
We can't put it in our show!
Let's put it in our show, yeah yeah yeah.
Romance... hmm. Romance.
Romance.
Guess we need to break free out of this place.
[Dropped Out of School Musical]
[The following scene is as follows: Croy and Gibriella are at a party. Croy loves basketball and Gibriella is not like other girls... a fictional tale of song and basketball.]
I don't want to sing. I'm just a normal boy.
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game. I can't sing! I'm just Croy.
Get it together, Gibriella. We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college.
I'm not like other girls. I just want to stay at home and read books.
ばかみたい 子供なのね
I've been a fool, you're such a child
夢を追って傷ついて
You got hurt chasing dreams
嘘が下手なくせに
You're so bad at lying, but still
笑えない笑顔みせた
Show me that unconvincing smile
I love youもろくに言わない
You don't say "I love you" enough
口下手でほんまに不器用
You're always awkward with your words
なのになのに行うして
So how did you ever
サヨナラは言えたの
Find the words to say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, no good, no good at all
あんたが好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much
どれだけ強いお酒でも
No matter how much strong alcohol I drink
歪まない思い出が
These unyielding memories are
ばかみたい
Just foolish
ばかみたい 本当バカね
I've been a fool, I'm such an idiot
あんた信じるばかりで
Always believing in you
強い女のふり
Putting on the front of a strong woman
切なさの夜風浴びる
Taking in the heartbreaking night breeze
一人になって
I've been alone
3年が過ぎ
for three years now,
街並みさえも
even the cityscape
変わりました
has changed.
なのに
And yet...
なのにどうして
and yet, why is it...
未練だけ
only my regrets
置き去り
are left behind?
ほんまに
You really
ろくな男やない
aren't a good man.
揃いの
Our matching
指輪外します
rings, I'll take them off.
ざまあみろ
Serves you right,
せいせいするわ
it's a relief.
いい加減
Enough is enough,
待ってても
even if I wait,
ばかみたい
I'm such a fool.
だめだね
It's no good,
だめよ
no good,
だめなのよ
no good at all.
あんたが
I love you,
好きで好きすぎて
I love you way too much.
どれだけ
No matter how much
強いお酒でも
strong alcohol I drink,
歪まない
they won't fade,
思い出が
these memories...
ばかみたい
I'm such a fool.
ほんまに
You really
ろくな男やない
aren't a good man.
揃いの
Our matching
指輪外します
rings, I'll take them off.
ざまあみろ
Serves you right,
せいせいするわ
it's a relief.
なんなのよ
What are they for,
この涙
these tears?
ばかみたい
I'm such a fool.
Whoa, yeah, yeah! Musicals is where it's at.
I think... I think this could really be it.
This is gonna get us the big dollars.
Yeah, hopefully... the big mouse is not gonna sue us.
Ten billion dollars!
What big mouse?
Don't worry about it.
Ten billion dollars! Yeah, it's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too,
you know, just for variety, so they can't shut us down.
A variety show?
Yeah.
Like a variety game show?
Yeah!
The Autofister Games.
The Autofister... physical games!
Games. Physicals.
105!
But first, a word from our sponsors.
Whoa!
Slow down there, partner!
Hold your horses! Don't you think you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and full-screen our video instead, because...
...we are about to show you the new hottest thing in town!
Introducing the...
Autofister Network!
Get it? 'Cause it's Autofister Network, but this is our merch.
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you all of our cool fun merch before it goes live!
We've got Cemimis!
Gimimis!
Grems!
Otomos!
And this neat acrylic stand of the both of us!
Yay!
And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to get the limited set with a card signed by both of us!
Woohoo! It will be live at these exact times, so make sure to check it out then!
Coming soon to a stream near you!
And we're back from our commercial break!
Thank you everyone for waiting!
Welcome back to the official...
...Autofister...
オートフィスター！
Autofister!
100！ 100！
100! 100!
And with us we have our lovely contestants...
Bae!
Okay, I'm gonna win! Hey!
Su!
すーちゃん、がんばるわ！
Su-chan, will do her best!
Towa!
トワ様。
Towa-sama.
Today, as said before, we are here to find out who's the ultimate winner of...
Physical Autofister 100!
As explained before the commercial break,
each contestant will have to compete in our physical obstacle course of fun!
Fun!
If you are just now tuning in, here is a quick recap.
Everyone starts in a line, you have to run to the other side while avoiding all obstacles,
and do a quick little physical activity.
Grab a question from a dragon, who telepathically gives it to you in your brain,
run back and answer a question.
We'll do four rounds, and the person with the most points
at the end of four rounds is the winner!
Okay, well, everyone, get into position!
I think something's very big. What is this?
So, so, as said before, of course,
since a lot of these questions will be in English,
Bae has a handicap.
She has a handicap. Very, very difficult questions.
What is this? Nice! Nice!
Everyone in position?
Yes, yes. The first round...
the first round is you run over there and do five jumping jacks.
Five jacks.
走って、5ジャンプやって...
Run, do five jumps...
質問取って、走って帰る？
take the question, and run back?
Okay, ready?
Three, two, one, go!
1、2、3、4、5！
One, two, three, four, five!
Su got first! First!
I was betrayed!
Please read the question out loud.
Okay, uh...
I like, uh... strawberry!
Yeah! She had to name a fruit!
Name a fruit! Fruit! Strawberry!
One point!
You can leave your questions over here.
Hey! Hey!
No, no, no, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Well, next round...
Next round! Is everyone ready? No, no, we have to explain.
Yeah, but is everyone ready for the next round?
Do we crab walk like this?
Crab walk like this!
Crab walk!
What?!
Crab walk and five squats.
5スクワット？クラブウォークして5スクワット？
Five squats? Crab walk and five squats?
Wait, do they have to jump? No, they can walk.
Jump! They have to jump! Okay, okay.
帰る時もこれ？
On the way back as well?
帰る時もな。
On the way back too.
Okay, everyone ready?
Three, two, one, go!
1、2、3、4、5！
One, two, three, four, five!
Hey, hey! Who was first?!
Bae got first! First!
Okay, come on. Oh, I ripped the mind telepathy paper.
Hey, you can't rip our telepathy paper.
13 times 6... 78!
Yes! She's actually really good at math!
She is good at math! Wow!
またバナナ！ またバナナなんだけど！
Banana again! It's banana again!
え？ 2回連続バナナなんだけど！
Eh? Two bananas in a row!
Two banana questions!
おい、日本語書いてあるじゃねえか！
Hey, there's Japanese written on here!
What?! I was given a handicap because the questions were in English, they're written in Japanese!
Hey! But the questions...
Okay, okay, we gotta keep it rolling, guys. Keep it rolling!
Do I still have to go around and around?
Those are the rules by our producers, who are not us.
On my telepathy paper, the next one is...
...sexy walk!
Sexy walk? Sexy, sexy!
If it's not sexy enough, do we get disqualified, do we have to start again? Yes!
What? Please make up your mind. We'll see, we'll see.
And three push-ups!
腕立て伏せ3回？
Three push-ups?
And then sexy walk back!
Sexy walk! Sexy walk!
Sexy walk? Sexy jump? Sexy jumps! Sexy jumps!
もしセクシーさが足りなかったら万が一やり直しって言われてるから。
They said if our sexiness is lacking, we might have to redo it.
What?! Sexiness is lacking?!
Sexy! Sexy! Sexy!
任せろ、任せろ！
Leave it to me!
Towa-sama's sexy!
Okay.
Okay! Everyone ready?
Three, two, one, go!
Sexy, Bae! Sexy!
You tried to make it sexy.
いち、に...
One, two...
さん、に、さん！
Three, two, three!
トワ様！
Towa-sama!
Oh, sexy!
Sexy! Sexy!
That's how you do it!
Sexy, Towa-chan!
Are? Sexy Bae?
Wait, sexy Bae?
I'm sexy Bae.
Again! Are?
Again! Wait...
セクシーじゃない。
It wasn't sexy.
You tried, but...
Bae, you only have to do it on the way there. On the way back you can go straight.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey, don't help the contestant!
Name a flower!
パンジー
Pansy!
Oh! Yeah! Pansy!
知ってる？
Do you know it?
Yeah! 良かった！
Yeah! Thank goodness!
One, one, one.
Wait, Jiji, Jiji. Have you been counting the points?
Yeah, 1-1-1.
Oh, really? 1-1-1?
1-1-1.
Oh, tiebreaker!
Okay, okay, okay.
最後のポイントは...
The last point is...
Are you ready?
100 points? 100 points!
Can I get rid of this?
No! Last round!
Do this... You have to do this well.
Lunge walk.
Eh?! きた！
Eh?! It's tough!
やばい...
This is bad...
And then...
来た、来た、来た！
They're here, they're here, they're here!
3 times!
Okay, okay!
How many times? 3 times!
三回、三回、三。
Three times, three times, three.
And then three... Eh?!
Wow, you guys look good!
Woah!
頑張ろう。
Let's do our best.
分かりましたか？
Do you understand?
Okayです。
Yes, okay.
しんどそう、なんか。
It looks tough somehow.
Me too. Me too.
Can I...
Can I throw this?
No! No, no, no!
Come on, come on. Bae, fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
Three...
Two, one, go!
Go! Go!
Hoy, hoy! Get to the front!
どうして？どうして？
Why? Why?
Are your knees touching?
Towa-sama is fine, she's doing her best.
いち、に...
One, two...
に、さん！
Two, three!
Woah! This is close!
Okay, okay.
Hold on, hold on!
Oop! Oop! Oop!
Towa-sama!
Towa-sama won!
Yay!
Wait, let's wait for Bae to come back.
Oh, Bae, come on.
Come on, Bae!
We can answer, Bae, come on.
Come on Bae, we can't decide the winner until you get over here.
Hoy, hoy, hoy!
Hoy, hoy, hoy! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, you need a high five.
High five!
Hey, squad over here.
Hey, squad.
Come on, come on.
All right, here is your question.
Say a French word!
French? French.
Do you know?
Do you know any French?
Bonjour!
Wow! Yeah!
Winner!
Towa is the winner!
Our winner today!
Yes!
Yeah, we did it!
Wait, what?
(Laughter)
Well, I guess some contestants have something to complain about no matter what we do.
Yeah, we did our best.
They should try to do the last level, it was like insane!
やってみないと、やってみないと、一瞬。
You have to try it, you have to try it, even for a moment.
一瞬も回って、結構しんどいよ。
Spinning even for a second is pretty tough.
No, no, no. Stop, stop, stop.
Bae only.
Ah, Bae only, Bae only.
Bae, only you.
Security! Security!
Yeah, security!
Security, I got her.
Security!
Now, let's give our winner her crown!
Yay!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Our winner!
This is not fair!
Please leave! Tiebreaker, tiebreaker!
This is Bae!
This is Sue!
This is Towa-sama!
And you're watching...
The Autofist Network!
Mmh...
The rat sucked.
Yeah.
She should go back to the gym or something.
She should go back to school...
...and retake PE.
Yeah, but Towa-sama was really strong.
Wow, she even got the cool crown! Amazing.
And Sue is so cute.
So cute!
Yeah!
Yeah, also the hosts were amazing.
Really charismatic, so...
...beautiful!
Every time they were on the screen, I was...
...electrified!
I think this is what's going to get us the funding.
Yeah, I think we're going to get 10 million dollars for this one.
And the more budget they have, the more difficult the...
...challenges can get, and then the death, you know...
...penalty...
...can be even greater.
Anyways, what if...
...anime...
...but live-action?
I don't feel so good.
Cecilia, I don't feel so good...
I'm so tired, Gigi.
Me too. I'm so tired...
...from working so hard.
We've been working so hard, making so many shows.
I'm so sleepy.
And we're always recording in the studio every single day.
I always wanted a tea party.
If only someone would invite me to their tea party.
You know what, actually, I have been preparing something.
Is it this background?
This really realistic background that you probably stole from the internet?
Who said I stole it? I stole it.
You stole it from the internet?
Yeah, and this is my tea party, so welcome in.
It's, but yeah, I have another surprise.
You have a surprise for your tea party?
Yeah. We're models.
We're what? Where's me? Where's me?
You know what? We got some graphics update.
Oh, a graphic update?
You want to see?
You want to see? I want to see! Me!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's me!
Cecilia Immergreen, from Hololive EN Justice!
Spin to win!
You look great!
Oh, thanks!
You look freaking amazing!
I guess, I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh my god.
I look so good, look at my shoes.
You look so good! Wow!
Hey Gigi, come on, come on in, it's okay.
Oh, I get one too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gigi Murin, everyone!
It's Gigi Murin from Hololive English Justice!
I'm so happy to be here!
Wow, you look good too, you look great!
I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Yeah.
Look at my shoes too.
Wow, wow, wow.
They look good, those look kind of hard to walk in actually, that's crazy.
No, I'm a natural.
Let me sit down.
Sit down, sit down, sit down already.
And together, we are...
Autofist! Autofist Network! Yeah!
Finally, we get some time to relax. Wow, you look really good.
Ah, thank you. You look really good too.
Oh, we're hugging again. Oh.
I just can't, I just really like hugging you. I can't help that I keep hugging you.
Really like hugging, I guess. Oh, my hood came off, that's fine.
I'm so excited!
So excited.
I'm really happy to be here.
Are you hungry?
I'm really hungry, will you feed me?
Okay, I'll feed you, I'll feed you.
Say ah.
Ah.
Oh, wait, actually...
Oh my god.
Wait, oh, I'm really hungry too, I guess.
Oh my god, I'm really, I'm... Oh, you're getting this all over me. It's getting really messy.
Oh, why is it getting on your face too? Ew!
It tastes really good.
Let me feed you again.
Oh, do you mind? I've got my spit on it, you don't mind, do you?
Wait, wait, let me wipe that off, you, you got something on the side of your mouth, let me just, let me just get that for you.
Are you so...
Let me get it off of you too.
Oh, you have something on your mouth.
Oh, okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough.
Thirsty?
Um, I'm thirsty. I'm really thirsty.
Okay, I'll, I'll pour you some tea.
Ooh.
I'm really excited.
Here's your tea.
Eeee, it's really hot!
Oh, be careful, be careful.
Oh my god, it's really, oh my god, it's really hot! Oh, it's really on my, oh...
Oh god, oh, it's all over my body.
Oh no, you spilled it!
Oh my god! Oh my god, it burns! Atsui, atsui!
Oh my god, I am...
Oh no! I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now!
Why did you do that to me? You're burning me!
I'm sorry, ow, ow, let me, let me wipe it off of you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that. I just got really overzealous.
Mm, but it's really good now it's cooled down.
You like it? What type of tea is it?
It's like a note, a little floral note on it. Here, try some.
Try from my finger. Try from my finger.
How does it taste?
Yummy.
Mmm, that's really good.
Okay, okay, that's, that's enough.
I finished my cup. It was really, it was really delicious.
If Liz was here, she would tell us that after having a really good meal, we should work out.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so we should work out.
Let's get up.
Let's go stand over there.
Yeah, let's stand by the horse.
That horse is really amazing.
You're making so much noise.
Sorry, my shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I... I want to do...
You know what, I want to do 50 push-ups.
Me? I really want to...
I really wanted to do 50 push-ups... Okay, okay, wait. I changed my mind.
What'd you change your mind to?
I want... I want, um, 50 lunges.
50 lunges?
Oh, your knee hurts?
Oh... I think, yeah, I got into an accident, uh, about 200 years ago.
Did you get hit by a car?
I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Oh, okay.
I guess that's just how it is.
You know what, Chichimuri...
Don't touch me!
Stop touching me.
Don't touch me! What?
Oh my god, why are you always doing that? Why are you always fighting with me?
You're just...
You always fight! No! No!
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you so much!
I hate your hair!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. I got... Sorry, I was getting mean. I was acting out. Do you forgive me?
I... I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling...
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
I didn't mean to. Can you kiss my knee, please?
I guess, oh, I feel really good now.
Do you feel better?
I feel better.
And I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Oh, me too, actually.
Yeah, so sleepy.
I'm so sleepy.
Ah, but there's only one bed. What should we do? Should we get in together?
I... I guess so. I guess we'll get in together. Let me just take off my shoes.
Oh yeah, I think it'd be really, really weird to get into bed with shoes on.
Yeah, that would be strange.
Let me help you. Let me fluff this pillow for you. Oh, you look so...
Here you go, Princess.
Okay, let me... Let me just lay down. Oh, let me get into bed... I'll take my shoes off too.
I'm already getting so comfortable.
Please, please don't go to bed without me!
I'm so tired. If someone doesn't get into bed quick, I'm just going to fall asleep without you.
Oh, no, don't, don't! It's just my... my achy achy bones, I'm trying to get into bed, please!
I guess your knee really hurts still.
It does.
Oh, I feel so comfortable.
Thanks for coming to my tea party, Chichimuri.
Thanks for inviting me, Cece.
Good night.
Wait, why are we holding hands?
I guess we're holding hands.
It's because I... I get scared in the dark.
Oh, of course, yeah.
So, I'm glad that we have each other. Good night, Cece.
Good night, Chichi.
I'm Cece!
And I'm Chichi!
And you're watching...
The Autofister Network!
Um... Hmm.
I don't know if that's going to make us any money.
Well, onto the next idea!
みんなが大好きっ!!
Everyone's favorite...!!
延々続行 ルララ Miracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la miracle sing time
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, it's the absolute best way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy
届けたい 精一杯のsoulを
I want to convey my soul with all I have!
どうしよう オートマティックに決められてる
What can we do, it's been decided for us automatically
時間割じゃ追っつかないの
We can't follow this timetable
の 夢無限 したいこと怒濤
Billowing waves of us infinite dreamers
廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
dash out and assemble in the hallway
の お行儀悪かったらsorry! でもなりふりも構わずに
Sorry if my manners are bad! But don't mind how I look
どっぷりハマっちゃうplay
I'm totally addicted to playing
キラリって もしかこれが青春
a sparkle, maybe this is what youth is
ever ever...Forever Shine
Ever ever... forever shine
ほんとに大好きっ!!
I really love you!!
テンション上昇 ルララ Powerful Gig Time
It's a tension-rising lu-la-la powerful gig time
ハートっ!!て ハートっ!!て ワクワク探す天才
My heart is, my heart is, an excitement-seeking genius
アレッ!?って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if I say "huh!?" or start racking up misses
放ちたい 湧いてくるbraveを
I want to set free my boiling bravery
しかけるトレモロ 応えるフラム
On with the tremolo, followed by flam
いいじゃん いいじゃん ノリノリでいんじゃない
Ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome to feel so good
ハッピーはいつだってね “今”感じるもの
I'm always so happy, it's the way "now" feels
生きろ乙女 本能で、裸の
Live on, fair maidens, with your bare instincts
のーのーのー 終わるの？
No, no, no, is it ending?
始まるの！
It's beginning!
どうしよう オートマティックに
What should I do? Automatically...
決められてる時間割じゃ追っつかないの
...the schedule we're given is too packed to keep up with!
C!
ユーモア ナチュラル めくるめく笑い
Humor, natural, dizzying laughter,
ウケ過ぎでお腹痛い
my stomach hurts from laughing too much!
T!
呼吸ぴったしexcellent! でも苦手な
Our breathing is perfectly excellent! But there was still...
リフまだあったの
...a riff I wasn't good at.
E!
特訓つきあってくれる？
Will you practice with me?
も少し門限までだって帰りたくない
It's almost curfew, but I don't want to go home yet!
never never... can't say good-bye
めちゃめちゃ大好きっ！！
I love you so, so much!
超絶ぞっこん ルララ Wonderful Show Time
I'm totally crazy about you! Lu-la-la, wonderful show time!
音楽って 音楽って もう私達まんま
Music is, music is already just who we are!
スタンディングオベーション賞 オーディエンスなしでも
Standing ovation award, even without an audience,
奏得たい 瞬間のReal
we want to play this moment for real!
昨日の後悔って 明日の心配って...
Regretting yesterday, worrying about tomorrow...
ぶっちゃけぶっちゃけ 誰得？何得？
Honestly, honestly, what's the point? Who does it help?
ラッキーはいつだってね “今”つかむもの
Good luck is always something you grab in the "now"!
欲張り乙女 与えられん、さらば！
Be greedy, girls! If you aren't given it, say farewell!
さらば！
Farewell!
どんな本も書いてない
It's not written in any book,
授業じゃちょっと教わらん
and they don't teach it in class,
だけど一生忘れない
but I'll never forget it for the rest of my life.
この世にないと思ってた奇跡
The miracle I thought didn't exist in this world,
一緒にね歌えば 信じられるんだ
when we sing together, I can believe in it!
強くなれるんだ
I can become stronger!
みんなが大好きっ！
I love you all!
延々続行 ルララ Miracle Sing Time
Continuing on forever! Lu-la-la, miracle sing time!
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, it's the ultimate way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even if the song is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy,
届けたい 精一杯のsoul
I want to convey my soul with all I have...
等身大のlifeを
...along with our larger-than-life life!
せーの！
One, two...
今日は昨日みたい？ 明日は今日みたい？
Is today like yesterday? Is tomorrow like today?
大丈夫大丈夫 楽しかったら大正解
It's okay, it's okay! If it was fun, then it's a huge success!
ロッカーはいつだってね “今”やんちゃ盛り
Rockers are always in their rebellious phase in the "now"!
進め乙女 抱きしめて、希望を
Onward, girls! Embrace your hopes!
大好き！
I love you!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for loving me too!
歌うよ 歌うよ 心込めて今日も歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, I'll sing with all my heart again today!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for loving me too!
歌うよ 歌うよ 愛を込めてずっと歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, forever I'll sing with all my love!
Please hold.
We will soon be changing the channel.
We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait.
The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated...
...as the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel...
...because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote...
...cause we will be doing it!